The Music and Feeling go on Forever.
Grease 2 is a comedy, music, romance film directed by Patricia Birch.
It's 1961, two years after the original Grease gang graduated, and there's a new crop of seniors
and new members of the coolest cliques on campus, the Pink Ladies and T-Birds.
Michael Carrington is the new kid in school - but he's been branded a brainiac.
Can he fix up an old motorcycle, don a leather jacket, avoid a rumble with the
leader of the T-Birds, and win the heart of Pink Lady Stephanie?
Michael Carrington, played by Maxwell Caulfield.
Stephanie Zinone, played by Michelle Pfeiffer.
Paulette Rebchuck, played by Lorna Luft.
Sharon Cooper, played by Maureen Teefy.
Rhonda Ritter, played by Alison Price.
Dolores Rebchuck, played by Pamela Adlon.
Grease 2 is a 1982 American musical romantic comedy film and a standalone sequel to the 1978 film
Grease, adapted from the 1971 musical of the same name by Jim Jacobs and Warren Casey.
Originally titled More Grease, the film was produced by Allan Carr and Robert Stigwood, and directed and
choreographed by Patricia Birch, who choreographed the original stage production and prior film.
The plot returns to Rydell High School two years after the original film's graduation, with a largely
new cast, led by Maxwell Caulfield and Michelle Pfeiffer in her first starring role.
The film was released in United States theaters on June 11, 1982, and grossed $15 million against a
production budget of $11 million, a far cry from its predecessor's $132 million domestic box office.
Despite breakthrough roles for Pfeiffer, Adrian Zmed, and Christopher McDonald, the film received mostly mixed
reviews from critics; however, Grease 2 maintains a devoted fan base decades after its release.
The film is now regarded as a cult classic.
The film explores themes of musical, talent show, motorcycle, woman director.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional.